["Here Comes Trouble" playing]
[narrator] Previously on Love Island USA...
One boy opened up.
I can't wait to build
our relationship like a Lego set.
-One brick at a time.
-I love that.
He said. like.
she only had friendship vibes with me.
And one girl...
-What the hell?
-I didn't see him as a competition.
...shut things down.
I don't see it going romantic anymore.
She has shown me
she is someone you cannot trust.
and you have shown me the same.
-She did tell you it was only friendship?
-Yes.
Ariana Madix tested the couples...
Girls. what is your boy's body count?
[Leonardo] Oh. fuck.
-Thirteen.
-Tell her to reverse her answer.
-[Hannah] Thirty-one.
-No. I thought she said 17.
So. 71.
...and raised the stakes.
Our winners. Marco and Hannah.
Congratulations.
[all clap. cheer]
As our winning couple.
you will not face the public vote.
You have also won the power to choose
one other couple to be safe.
Leo and Anna.
[Ariana] Victor and Carmen.
Bergie and Kassy.
Keenan and Kay Kay. Harrison and Destiny.
you will all face the public vote.
♪ I tried to tell ya
Watch out ♪
How's that for a bombshell?
♪ Here comes trouble ♪
Tonight...
I don't care about your feelings.
Why you keep making shit happen?
Confrontation.
Bro. don't come heated yelling at me.
This is bullshit. I'm over it.
Fucking douche-bag.
I don't trust you.
I don't want to see you around me.
Fuck.
And the decision
of the nation.
"America has been voting
for their favorite couples.
Those with the fewest votes
risk being dumped tonight."
[theme song playing]
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
["You Can Have Every Little Bit" playing]
♪ I cannot wait until the weekend ♪
♪ Wanna see you right now ♪
Welcome to Love Island USA.
Hannah and Marco won Mr. and Mrs..
earning immunity from the first dumping
for themselves
and Anna and Leonardo.
Losing Mr. and Mrs.
means either Kassy and Bergie.
Kay Kay and Keenan. Destiny and Harrison.
or Carmen and Victor
will soon be sat on a plane home
in total silence. their dreams in tatters.
which ironically. is just what it's like
being an actual Mr. and Mrs.
So. how does everybody feel?
You know. we're at the vulnerable position
right now.
I think you two
are more than safe.
Mine is not working.
We're coming down to one of us.
-We have a dumping in 24 hours.
-[Kassy. Destiny] Mm-hmm.
I'm gonna say. honestly. like.
I know it's me and Bergie.
-You never know.
-Absolutely.
You never know.
[Kay Kay] How you feeling?
You good?
I feel good.
I'll be so happy if I get to stay.
But I also know. like...
-Yeah.
-Like. just realistically.
neither of us are in good couples.
you know what I mean?
I'm sad about potentially
leaving the villa.
I feel like in here.
all your relationships.
like you're driving down the road
and you reach a fork and it either goes
friendship or romance.
And I feel like all of my relationship
with the men in here have hit that fork
and gone friendship.
besides me and Bergie.
And I've kind of been waiting
to see if it could grow.
Hannah and Marco and Anna and Leonardo.
who are immune from the dumping.
head to the sofa.
Or as it will now be known. "smug corner."
[Anna] Are you upset? How are you feeling?
[Hannah] I'm very conflicted.
Why?
I feel like everyone feels like
I'm the one who should've been chosen.
You get what I mean?
-No. nobody feels like that.
-I don't feel like that at all.
And I feel like you guys have...
-You just got started in your connection.
-Yeah.
You're in a couple and you're progressing
and things are good between you guys.
All Anna talks about is like.
"I really like him." [chuckles]
-[Anna] Don't tell him that to his face.
-[Leonardo laughs]
Leave some mystery.
And I think to see
a couple go is never easy.
It's gonna be hard.
And I established a relationship
with everyone that's left.
-[Leonardo] Yeah.
-But I knew one thing I couldn't do
is turn my back knowing
that you two aren't safe. so...
-Yeah.
-[Anna] Yeah.
I fucking love you. Hannah.
-I love you. too.
-I love you. my bro.
I'm grateful for everything.
-But I just know that I have you guys...
-[Hannah] Mm-hmm.
-...for the rest of my life.
-[Marco] Mm-hmm.
-Like. I will always be grateful for you.
-[Hannah mumbles. indistinct]
Destiny's given gold dealer Harrison
her undivided attention.
And he's given her this fetching
24-karat chunky necklace.
Only $3.000 over 24 easy monthly payments.
-Oh. my gosh. I'm so proud of us.
-Yeah. we did a great job.
-We did a great job.
-[laughs]
That's for sure.
I cannot stop smiling about it.
Honestly. we are the newest here.
The fact that we were tied with the couple
that's been here since the second day.
Yeah.
-And I think that shows a lot.
-I think that too.
It makes me really happy.
I'm not gonna lie.
Bottom line. we did a great job.
We did a great job.
Yeah. we just need to work
on each other's turn-ons.
I'm so elated.
Like. I cannot stop smiling.
That game solidified a lot for me
about just the understanding that's there
and the dynamic that we have.
And it's clear to see it's not a facade.
There's no way you can fabricate
a connection like that.
-We look so good together.
-Yeah. we do.
Because I really am happy here.
I'm no longer... I'm finally no longer
the stage where I'm talking about
early days either.
-Okay? [laughs]
-Shut the fuck up.
-I really do like you...
-You like me.
I like your little chocolate ass.
I ain't gonna lie.
-Yeah. I like you back.
-I do.
-You better. goddamn.
-I better?
Yeah. you ain't got no choice now.
I ain't got no choice?
Why I ain't got no choice?
-You got me progressing.
-[chuckles]
So. you ain't got no choice.
-We progressing?
-No. for sure.
I love it here.
You better. I love it here too. goddamn.
I'm glad you wore the black. too.
Yeah. we look cute. We look sexy together.
Fuck. yeah.
Bergie wants to know
exactly where he stands with Carmen.
As far as I can see.
on about 50 square foot
of low-quality imported Astroturf.
-How are you?
-Doing good. how are you?
-Good.
-Actually. I'm not good.
-but we'll talk about that.
-Oh. what's up?
Okay. So. earlier today.
we ended our conversation
with the whole Victor situation.
Did you tell him. like.
we only had a friendship?
-No.
-No? Okay. so. like...
No. That's what I said.
and he was like. "You're right.
I shouldn't have said anything."
-We had a conversation about that.
-You and Victor did?
Yeah. with all the other guys and...
-Okay.
-Like. so...
But he made it seem like
you told him again that he...
And then he told me that you told...
I don't want any more drama
from this. you know?
-We had...
-I'm gonna grab him right now.
-No. no. No.
-No. I'm gonna go grab him.
-We can all talk together.
-No.
[Bergie] Can I give you
a compliment right now?
-Um. sure. what's up?
-You're a strong-ass woman.
-Thanks.
-Sure.
Do you want to meet me in the kitchen?
Yeah. I'll meet you in the kitchen.
Do you want to come for a chat
with Bergie and I real quick?
-Me?
-Yeah.
Sure.
[Carmen] So. I'm a little bit confused.
because I feel like...
When did I tell you
it was just friendship with Bergie?
Because apparently
it was said again tonight.
that I said that verbatim. That I told you
it was only friendship with him.
We already have talked about this.
What is the purpose of all of this?
Because you apologized to me
and said you didn't say that.
Why do we keep talking about this?
Like. this happened like a few days ago.
I have tried
to close this situation repeatedly.
I don't care anymore.
Be happy. You two. be happy.
Go over there. Like. do your thing.
One of the things is a competition
between you and me.
And then another competition
-So. you apologized...
-Once again. you have done the same thing.
So why do you apologize to me.
if you've done the same thing again?
Okay. can I finish speaking?
-Go ahead.
-You apologized to me.
and you're like. "You're right.
I shouldn't have gone to Bergie
and said that."
Why would you apologize
and go do it again?
-Like...
-I didn't do it again.
No. we were talking about
the whole conversation over there.
What I told him.
I went back to talk to him. It was like...
-When did I ever say I was closed off?
-What?
When did I ever say I was closed off?
I don't know what day it was
and all that stuff.
-The moment...
-I've never been closed off in here.
The moment that that happened.
we already have talk about that.
I went to talk to him because
he didn't explain everything to you.
-Why tonight?
-I'm not talk...
Did you not say it again?
-What happened tonight?
-No. no. no. no.
So. we were talking about
that conversation over there.
Why you keep...
Why you keep making shit happen?
-This conversation was...
-Okay. stop.
-Let's calm down. This is all so intense.
-I'm calm down.
-The thing is. he...
-I don't think anyone
should be speculating on my feelings.
I'll share them when I want to.
I don't care about your feelings.
I'm not speculating about your feelings.
-I already apologized. I already...
-If you don't care. that's fine.
I'm gonna finish this
conversation with Bergie.
-But I know where we stand.
-Then don't call me.
You don't come to apologize to me
and come to talk to her again.
Don't talk to me anymore. dude.
-Calm down.
-So. for what do you come to apologize?
-Let us finish this conversation.
-I'm calm down. but why that?
-You. Bergie. take a deep breath.
-[sighs]
I'm sorry that I brought him over here
and he acted that way.
-I'm so sorry that he...
-No. it's okay.
...escalated it.
What is going on. like. with the boys?
Like. what was said tonight?
Like. why is it... this all such
a big thing? What's going on?
Okay. so... Oh. my gosh.
-I'm sorry. I'm... Ever since...
-No. it's okay.
It's been a whole thing tonight. Um...
Yeah. So. like.
there have... Okay. eventually. just...
-[sighs] Fuck. I... I don't...
-Do you want to take a minute?
-Should we talk in a little bit?
-Can we talk tomorrow?
-Yeah. no. let's sleep on it and stuff.
-Okay. Yeah.
Sorry. I know it sucks. but...
[sighs]
Bro. don't come heated yelling at me.
-Listen.
-I'm not dealing with this.
-This is bullshit. I'm over it.
Can I talk or are you leaving?
Can I talk? If you talk.
you should listen to me.
I want to leave. I don't want her to stay.
I don't want her to stay. [chuckles]
Bergiestocks.
Bro. I'm so fucked up right now.
Fucking talk to me. baby boy.
Look like it was...
-[Leonardo] What the fuck is happening?
-[Keenan] There's a lot going on.
-Fuckin' douche-bag!
-I don't know what is happening now.
-What is going on?
-[Victor] You can talk.
-Explain.
-He hasn't said anything.
He hasn't had a chance to say anything.
Do you need time to clear your head?
-Fuck it. I'm here.
-Goddamn.
Fuck it. I'mma take a seat.
[Leonardo] I have no idea what's going on.
We... We're not going to...
Look at me. Berg. Berg. Berg. Berg.
-[Marco chuckles]
-We're not gonna interrupt you.
Say your piece. I won't...
No one's gonna jump in.
Say exactly what happened.
Okay. Earlier today.
when I was on the Breathe bench.
I told Carmen towards
the end of our conversation.
"I almost didn't pursue you
because Victor told me that
you only saw a friendship vibe with us."
-Yes. we went through that.
-Yes. friendship...
But you told her... but you... you told her
that I have talked to you
in front of all the other guys.
That's why she pulled me aside.
Why do you have to go like
a fuckin' puppy behind her
to tell her that I pulled you aside
and I have belittled you?
That I came here like a fucking macho man
to make you feel small and all that stuff.
When we... The only thing that I have
seen is to state my... make my statement.
that I don't want to see you.
I don't want... I don't trust you.
-I don't want to even see you around me.
-[Bergie] Yeah.
How... How did we come in here
and talk about trust
and what stays between these doors
with these men here?
How did we talk about that
and then you go out
and say that Victor pulled you aside
in front of all the boys?
I don't even have any interest
in her anymore.
and you're still causing me problems.
What the fuck?
-He's cool off this girl.
-I don't even want to be with her.
You need... What you... [sighs]
You need some time. bro?
-I need some time.
-[Keenan] Go ahead. just take a walk.
You know what I'm saying?
Just take a walk.
[Victor chattering]
♪ I'm gonna stand up strong ♪
♪ I'm gonna stand up tall ♪
[scoffs] What the fuck?
♪ I'm gonna stand my ground
Until I've taken down your prison wall ♪
♪ I'm gonna kill 'em with love ♪
♪ And be the better man ♪
[grunts. sighs] Fuck.
["Walk All over Me" playing]
At first. he felt like.
"Bergie ain't competition.
I'm not worried about Bergie."
But see. Bergie. he been actually
focusing on what's important.
So. guess what?
That bruised his little dick-ass ego.
He's a little kid
that needs. like. reinforcement.
and he just want to be like...
"Whatever you need. I'm the good guy."
Like. yeah.
I know that you're not a malicious guy.
I know you had no badly intent.
Mmm. It was a tough situation.
[Hannah] Are you okay?
-Yeah.
-Yeah. we're good.
Don't fuck with Bergie.
No. I don't give a fuck.
-I just wanna still be here.
-[women chattering]
Yeah.
♪ How many times? ♪
-Yeah. are you?
-Are you sure?
-Yes. are you?
-Are you sure? Yeah.
But you guys wear these every day.
-No. we don't...
-Like I can see them.
♪ How many times can I? ♪
♪ Walk all over me? ♪
♪ Yeah. walk all over me ♪
♪ How many times can I? ♪
♪ Ooh. how many times? ♪
♪ How many times can I
Allow you to walk all over me? ♪
♪ Yeah. walk all over me ♪
♪ How many times can I? ♪
♪ I wonder. I wonder ♪
[music ends]
["In the Wild" playing]
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
♪ Drive away with me ♪
So. how did everybody sleep?
♪ Settle down with me ♪
The block was a little hot
last night. right?
But fuck it. it's a new day.
Yeah.
[Leonardo] You know. so let's try our best
to have a good time.
Kick it. do what we gotta do.
♪ It's too late ♪
[Keenan]
[Bergie] I'm gonna let it rock.
♪ You think that smile ♪
For him. he really doesn't
think there was any blame.
I'm like. "No. your reaction
is not acceptable."
I'm not gonna be spoken to that way.
Especially by a man.
[Leonardo]
It's gonna be a lot of drama today.
I think you're right.
[music ends]
Bergie was trying
to talk to Carmen a while ago
and she told him.
like. "I need some space."
Yeah. 'cause of the whole situation.
-It makes sense.
-Yeah.
Yeah. they need some space.
you know what I'm saying?
We on the same page with that.
He gonna... [splutters] He made the bed.
he gotta lie in it. goddamn it.
All that I'm gonna say. Ain't nobody care.
-I love him. but hey...
-Yeah.
Once he got...
Once it's over with. it's over with.
But he gotta own it right now.
It's gonna sting.
-Yeah.
-It's gonna sting.
It's tough. But. hey. fuck it.
-It is what it is though.
-Literally.
We're all here to learn something
about ourselves.
Right. That shit...
Like. at the end of the day. you know.
of course I don't wanna
see any of my boys get hurt.
I don't wanna see Carmen get hurt.
I don't wanna see anybody here get hurt.
You know. it gets deeper
when people confide in you.
people tell you stuff. like.
I love being helpful to everybody.
but it's difficult carrying
all these different emotions
and knowing what to say. what not to say.
That shit is not easy whatsoever.
It's... [sighs] It's tricky.
I love you. Bergie.
Thanks. Hannah.
-It's all gonna be okay. okay?
-100%.
This too shall pass.
I'm here to listen.
I feel like I... I put everybody
in a bad position. [splutters]
No. you didn't. That's the thing. Bergie.
You didn't put anyone...
You acted on how you felt. okay?
You didn't try to hurt anybody.
you weren't disrespectful and rude
towards anybody.
So. I don't want you to think
that you brought this on yourself.
because you didn't.
-There's a way to respect.
-Yeah.
We're all gotta... At the end of the day.
we're dating the same people.
It's gonna get weird.
but we could all at least
have that respect
to not talk to each other crazy.
You get what I'm saying?
Yeah.
It doesn't matter who said what.
who. whatever. whatever.
We all say stuff that we shouldn't have.
We all fuck up in that sense.
I'm not mad at Victor.
I just... I'm kind of mad
at how he reacted.
Carmen feels bad
because she feels like she put you
in an uncomfortable situation.
So. but who's the person
who doesn't feel bad?
[sighs]
Victor? But I... [stammers]
I don't want to say that. though.
-And I saw your face.
-Yeah.
It just made me... It broke my heart
-that somebody made you feel sad.
-Yeah.
You know what I mean?
And you don't deserve that. Bergie.
-Okay? [sniffles]
-Yeah.
'Cause you're a good guy.
You're a sweet guy.
-You would never try to hurt him.
-Yeah.
This man is just...
I think he's scrambling.
because we found out
that someone's gonna get dumped soon.
It just hit the fan for him.
and he's like.
letting all this anger out about that.
I hope this made you feel better.
-I needed to talk to somebody.
-I know it's a lot on your head.
I wish I... [sighs] You know.
we could have talked last night. but...
Hannah and I are definitely close.
Older sister. younger brother vibe.
for sure.
Obviously. I didn't like
how last night went at all.
But this morning. you know.
start a new day. um.
new conversations for sure.
And today I feel. like. just let it go.
Just have the best day of your life.
You don't know when you're leaving.
Let's have the best day that we can.
[Kassy] I was like. "Let me give him
his little space this morning."
Now I just wanna check up on him.
-See how he's doing?
-Yeah.
Because I'm pretty sure he's going around
and just kinda explaining
the situation or whatever.
I don't want him to blame himself either.
I mean. don't beat yourself up.
You made a mistake. We all make mistakes.
It is what it is. move past it.
And he will beat himself up about it.
And he's not a malice guy.
or anything. Like. no.
So. like. that's all we can do.
-[Kassy] Ay. ay. ay.
-[Keenan] God. it is so fucking hot.
-I guess I'll just wait on Bergie. then.
-[Leonardo] Huh?
I said I guess I'll just wait on Bergie
and talk to him.
-[Victor chatters]
-[Leonardo] Go get your man.
[Kassy groans]
-[Leonardo moans]
-[Kassy] Oh. no.
Everywhere I go.
Leo is giving me little hugs.
Looking at me like...
And I'm like. "Mmm." Like. we're like...
It's like he's trying to talk to me
with his eyes.
and with my eyes. I'm like. "Stop."
-[laughs]
-[men chattering]
You would never do cheesy eggs?
-No. fuck no.
-No?
I ain't gonna lie.
I only eat eggs for protein.
[phone chimes]
I got a text!
-Oh. my God. Ain't no way.
-I got a text!
-Marco got a text!
-[Marco] Holler it.
Scream it to the fuckin' rooftops!
-[Kay Kay] What's happening?
-Hey. I got a text!
[all laugh. cheer]
-[woman] Yeah!
-Let's see what the text is about.
"Hannah and Marco and Anna and Leonardo.
the four of you
are going on a double date.
#TheChosenOnes. #GetDownAndDirty."
-[Leonardo] Yeah!
-Ooh. [chuckles]
-[Hannah] Yeah. yeah. yeah.
-[Leonardo] Hey. hey. hey.
Let's go.
-Okay. What do I wear?
-[Anna. Leonardo chuckle]
[Kay Kay] What do y'all think it is?
-What are we wearing?
-[Marco] Go get ready!
[Keenan]
Them boys gotta get dressed. goddamn.
-Let's go. baby. Let's fuckin' go.
-Let's go.
Hey. hey. hey.
♪ I can't help myself
I like what I see ♪
♪ These expensive things
I attract to me ♪
I say something shortish.
so in case it's messy.
Oh. is it time for me
to bust out this fit?
-Have you seen me wear this?
-No.
I'm super pumped
to go with Marco because. like.
end of the day. he is my best friend.
like my brother in here.
I'm super excited to see
how this double date goes.
and I feel like it's gonna
be some type of competition
or something because
it's "down and dirty."
I said it's so hard for me
to get to know someone.
-Yeah.
-In. like. an enclosed space.
I'm very. like...
I like to do something with them.
-[Kay Kay] Yeah.
-That is wild.
Honestly. give me a lot of clarity too.
you know?
You can see him outside.
[Anna] Yeah. yeah. yeah.
It's our first date. so I'm excited to see
if it takes us on a deeper level
in our connection.
And it could just be sexual.
"Down and dirty."
-Wow.
-You never fuckin'...
With the shades. Marco.
I'm... I'm feeling it.
[Kay Kay]
Bring me a seashell or something.
Yes. I'll bring you a seashell.
Okay. let's go have fun.
Life is good. I'm grateful.
I don't care what the hell it is.
I'm just happy to go on a date with Marco.
Like. we haven't been on a date.
and I've been sharing a bed with the guy.
-[Hannah] Let's get out of here.
-Let's go.
[Hannah] Let's go.
Tell us everything when you get back!
-Love you!
-[Marco] Bye.
[Leonardo]
I'll leave out the important details.
-[all clamor]
-Thank you!
["Kiss Me Like Summer" playing]
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
I asked the date team
to sort out the filthiest.
dirtiest date we've ever seen.
So they stuck a bucket of mud
in the middle of a field.
and it's not quite what I meant.
-I've never seen some shit like this.
-[Marco. Hannah chuckle]
[Marco] Me neither.
So. who's breaking the cake?
-[Anna chuckles]
-I'll do it.
-[Marco] Oh. God.
-[Leonardo gasps]
[Leonardo] Here. I got extra.
Let me get you ready. [chuckles]
-[Leonardo groans]
-[Anna chuckles]
[Leonardo. Anna laughs]
Now you're doing it for him.
-Oh. thank you. Bobby. Thank you.
-Yeah. Yeah. yeah.
♪ Summer afternoon ♪
♪ Yeah. what a stunner
Way you move ♪
♪ Never be another like you ♪
♪ Yeah. 'cause you kiss me like summer
And I'm falling for you ♪
♪ Summer afternoon ♪
♪ Yeah. what a stunner... ♪
-[screams. laughs]
-[Anna chuckles]
♪ Never be another like you ♪
[Leonardo. Marco screaming]
[Hannah. Marco laughs]
♪ You kiss me like summer afternoon ♪
♪ Yeah. what a stunner
Way you move ♪
♪ Never be another... ♪
It definitely wasn't
what I expected at first.
-[Hannah] No. definitely not.
-I'm not enjoying this shit.
-[Marco. Hannah laughs]
-I was gonna say. [laughs]
[music ends]
Kassy is excited.
'cause earlier this morning.
Leonardo bared his soul to her.
There were a couple of verrucas
and the nails needed trimming.
but she didn't seem to mind.
Leo is being flirty with me.
This morning.
when I was sitting next to him.
he was putting his foot.
like. holding my...
Like that. holding my hand.
-His foot was holding my foot.
-You're making me uncomfortable.
-[laughs] Like. literally like that.
-[laughs] Hey. no.
-[laughs]
-And I was like this. "Mmm."
And he was just like...
It's taking a lot of effort for me
to not pull away right now
-so you can finish your demonstration.
-[laughs]
-Yeah.
-But the foot handhold is not my thing.
I was just like. "Mmm."
He broke the touch barrier
and now it's there.
Me and him are both like...
For me. I don't wanna admit
that I may have fucked up.
For him. he probably doesn't wanna admit...
-So it's like...
-He fucked up. yeah.
Obviously. I'm not gonna talk to him
right when he comes back
from a date with Anna.
And who knows?
Maybe this date. like. clarifies for him.
-Like. "No."
-Being with her. yeah.
I know Anna's gonna be pissed. but. like.
if Leo is showing interest. like.
what can I do?
Don't stress about nothing
till it's something.
Yeah.
Leo. I have no fucking clue
where his head is at.
but he's in a relationship with Anna.
But at the same time.
I wanna talk to him and see. like...
"Do... Are you thinking what I'm thinking?"
If I'm gonna do this again.
I'm gonna keep my cards
to my chest this time.
I'm just gonna fuckin' do what I wanna do.
[chuckles]
♪ Sugar-coated
when I called you up. babe ♪
♪ Do you feel me the same way? ♪
That was one for the books. for sure.
-Oh. yeah.
-[chuckles]
-Not my first ideal choice. but...
-Yeah.
So. I know.
in the game show last night.
there was a question.
"What do you think Leo's worst trait is?"
And I said. "flirting"
and you said that he gets a lot of girls.
So it just made me branch
out the question to think. like.
what would your family think of me
off of first impression?
Um. well. you did have
your pick of choices
when you first got here.
but at the end of the day.
I feel like you did the right thing.
And I feel once they get to know you.
they'll really learn to love you.
-Yeah. So. I'm in the doghouse right now.
-Yeah. [chuckles]
-Um...
-You got a little work to do.
-I ain't gonna lie.
-Oh. yeah. Oh. yeah.
[music ends]
♪ Say that you'll be here ♪
♪ Say that you'll be here
Till the end ♪
I expect us to. like.
do good in the challenge.
I didn't really expect us to win.
though. to be honest.
I kinda expected
other couples to know more.
-Really?
-Yeah.
So I was. like. pleasantly surprised.
but you were very confident.
-Extremely. [chuckles]
-[chuckles] Yeah. I know.
When you really listen to each other.
when you really relate.
that challenge was very easy.
I feel we're just like very similar
in a lot of things.
That's what I learned about you.
We feel the same about a lot of things.
which is good.
because I feel we can relate
on a lot of things.
We both like strawberries.
-Yeah. that's true.
-Do you want one?
-Sure.
-[chuckles]
[chuckles]
[exhales sharply]
-That's huge. [chuckles] Not a rocket.
-[chuckles]
Bite it.
Oh. that was hot.
-[muffled] Really?
-[chuckles]
[muffled] I'm not finished yet.
♪ If we lose or if we fall ♪
[both laughs]
♪ Will you keep standing through it all? ♪
[upbeat music playing]
Don't forget. you can join in
on the Love Island fun
and even control the action
by voting for your favorite couples.
Choose who you'd like to see
go on dates and much more.
[upbeat music playing]
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
So what did Hannah and Marco
and Anna and Leonardo
take away from their day at the spa?
They took stories. memories.
and four dressing gowns
they nicked from the changing rooms.
Yo!
[women cheer]
-[Kay Kay] Okay!
-Hi!
[Kay Kay] Howdy!
I wouldn't say it was super romantic.
um. when we were all muddy
in the hot spring.
To me. it was more like a fun little vibe.
-[Kay Kay] Was it sexy?
-Yeah!
-They was looking at each other.
-No. for real.
I was like. "Anna is my date."
-And you know how they are together.
-Yeah.
-Yeah. It was literally like...
-Uh-huh.
...they were dating
and we were dating. Shit.
We're putting on the mud
like warriors and shit. We're like. fuck...
We're doing the stupidest shit
just to have fun.
It felt good to get out of the villa.
It really did. It felt like it was needed.
-Yeah.
-I'm sure we all feel kinda that way.
Do you guys' bodies
feel different physically?
I feel like...
I feel like when I took a bath in here
the other day.
I just feel. like. at ease.
Feel like "zen."
-You guys...
-I'm about to make some tea. [chuckles]
Yeah! [laughs]
I swear to God.
["Scared of the Dark" playing]
The results of the public vote
are looming.
Let me tell you.
they're going to raise some eyebrows.
And Carmen's eyebrows
are already pretty up there.
Everything that happens
is gonna happen for a reason.
It's not even worth thinking
or stressing about
because any number of things could happen.
I don't think anyone's 100% confident
in how tonight's voting is gonna go.
[Victor] I kind of feel like
the captain of the Titanic. you know?
I should have seen
that. uh. iceberg coming.
-and now. we are sinking with the boat.
-[Marco laughs]
Is the iceberg reference to me?
-[Marco] Whoa!
-[Victor chuckles]
♪ Don't be scared of the dark ♪
I love you. girls.
-I love you too.
-We love you too.
The nerves are coming from the unknown.
Everybody ready?
I'm beyond happy not to be vulnerable.
Tonight is gonna be a very hard night
for everybody in the villa.
The stakes are high.
♪ Don't be scared of the dark ♪
[all chatter. chuckle]
Let's just live this last night together.
One of us is leaving.
so let's enjoy this memory of a lifetime.
-Let's do it. baby.
-[Bergie] Cheers to that!
-[Marco] Cheers to that.
-[Anna] We love you. Bergie.
Lovely toast from Bergie.
Coincidentally. toast is exactly
what one couple's going to be
after we find out the result
of the public vote.
I believe in you. America.
-How are you feeling?
-Good.
Me too. I'm at peace. I'm calm.
I mean. I'm not that worried
in the sense that. like.
I just think it's all gonna
work out for a reason. you know?
Do you wish you did anything different?
No. Everyone was like.
"Oh. I'm gonna get to know everyone."
-Yeah.
-But everyone was...
Once they. like...
They settled pretty quickly.
which. in the normal world.
doesn't happen. you know?
And even though I liked Victor
so much when we started.
I was like. "I'm not gonna make
promises I know I can't keep."
-Yeah.
-And I was right. 'cause...
-You know what I mean?
-Yeah.
Before Carmen arrived.
it was like. I don't feel any attraction
by any of the girls.
And then Carmen came and then
we connected on things and all that stuff.
And everything that she was saying.
it was like honey to my ears.
-Yeah. yeah.
-You know?
-This was like super intense.
-Yeah.
You don't understand
how intense all of this felt.
There's always gonna be conflict.
And that's the other thing as well.
is on the other end.
there's always going to be feelings.
-like true feelings. right?
-Mm-hmm.
'Cause there's always gonna be someone
that finds someone. you know?
Should I talk to Leo?
I think you should pull him
and see what he says.
And don't be disappointed
if he plays it safe.
-But. no. if it is...
-But do I know... The "what if's."
It's like.
"Why do you keep looking at me?"
Go pull him for a chat.
-Right now?
-Right now.
[sighs]
[Marco] How are we doing?
-How are you doing?
-[Marco] Getting closer. getting closer.
-[Leonardo] Holy shit!
[men laugh]
-How you doing?
Can I talk to Leo?
-[Victor] That was awesome.
-Yes. you can.
-I'll see you guys.
-[Victor] We'll see you later.
[Leonardo. Marco speak Spanish]
[sighs] Hey. Kassy.
-[Kassy. Leonardo speak Spanish]
-[Harrison laughs]
Wow.
Having a good night?
The fit is cool. I'm not gonna front.
-Do you like it?
-Yeah.
-Getting 2000's R & B.
-I like it.
-Thank you. I like it. too.
-[chuckles]
I like it too. a lot.
Okay. we're going upstairs.
You look cute.
Thank you. I thought I was giving grandpa.
-No.
-No? [laughs]
[Kassy. Leonardo speak Spanish]
[both chuckle]
So. how are you feeling?
I feel like calm. at peace.
-Yeah?
-What are you feeling?
I'm feeling good.
I've been. like. conflicted.
-About what?
-Um...
Things are going good in my relationship.
and I'm happy.
But at the end of the day. like.
just when I see you ever. I can't help.
like. my own natural feelings.
And there was a reason
why I picked you the first day.
["Sweet Talking Devil" playing]
[Kassy] I feel like we just
gravitate towards each other
even when we don't want to.
God. don't look at me.
-Why?
-'Cause you making it hard.
I'm not doing anything.
Now you got me feeling nervous as fuck.
-[chuckles]
-Um... [chuckles]
-Oh. my God. I feel horrible.
-[Kassy chuckles]
♪ We're a perfect match
When everything is burning down ♪
Everything about Anna is great.
There's not one bad thing
I could ever say about her.
But I just don't feel. like.
that same type of urge.
if that makes sense.
[whispering]
-Nah.
-Yeah.
[whispering]
-And he's like...
-[whispers. indistinct]
So. it was like. it would eat me alive
if I didn't share...
if I didn't tell that to you.
-Yeah.
-You know?
-Mm-hmm.
-But. um...
It's really hard to conceal how I feel.
I've always had
the initial attraction with Kassy.
but if those feelings progressin'.
I know I'm gonna have to tell Anna
because the last thing I want to do
is hurt a girl who's perfectly fine.
-I heard...
-Sit down. sit down.
I hear Kassy and Leo talking.
Full on flirting.
And he's talking shit about me.
-Damn!
-No!
-Pretty rough.
-We have it on record.
I'm not gonna cry.
I wish he had come to me
and say that he was uncomfortable.
-Yeah.
-And then for your own friends
to. like. just flirt it out.
[all clamor]
-Honestly. I feel like that's a lie.
-I'm not gonna cry.
I feel like he's not uncomfortable.
He's not. I know he's not uncomfortable.
I think he just maybe not like the fact
that I'm not a sexual person.
They're talking about cuddling.
And they're still talking.
Yeah.
♪ Sweet-talking devil ♪
♪ We're a perfect match... ♪
It's like. I. like.
couldn't get you
out of my head if I tried.
[moans]
And that's like being so straightforward.
No bullshit. And it's just. like.
I don't want to. like.
not say anything if you go home.
So. for me.
I feel like I owe it to myself.
I owe it to you to. like.
have the clarity in knowing that.
-I feel betrayed by two people.
-Yeah.
And two people that I really trust.
-I obviously...
-He never said anything to you?
Like. "I'm closed off. I'm not about her"?
I'm always like.
"No. Leo is my number one."
-[Kay Kay] Yeah.
-If I were to leave.
-it would be with him. Not. like...
-Yeah.
-What?
-Nothing.
Mmm.
-I'm trying to behave.
-Me too.
♪ When you say you want me ♪
♪ I forget that you're an animal
Who takes... ♪
Le.
-Come on. buddy.
-Go with them.
I'll meet you down there.
The boys just want to chat one last time
before the last thing. but that's fine.
Whatever.
-Fuck. he didn't leave.
-Fuck!
Fuck!
-You know what you're like?
-What?
You're like the apple
Adam and Eve shouldn't have ate.
but they definitely knew
they should have ate.
-Oh. yeah?
-Yeah.
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
It doesn't take a detective to work out
what Kassy and Leonardo
were up to on the balcony.
But Anna literally is a detective.
and she knows exactly
what they were up to on the balcony.
[Marco] Fuckin' hell. I look dumb.
-I saved them.
-[Keenan] Yeah.
Fuck.
-You know. come on.
-Why do I feel like
-I'm doing the walk of shame right now?
-[whistles]
[scoffs]
The fuck are you doing?
Having a conversation?
-[Keenan] Come on. baby boy.
-[Bergie] I'm gonna go.
-What?
-Come on. baby boy. You're not dumb.
You're not fuckin' dumb.
You're not kidding me.
Are you fucking kidding me?
-What?
-Come on. man.
Leo.
♪ In your eyes ♪
-[Carmen] Um...
-[Kay Kay] Kass.
They were in the kitchen.
They could hear everything.
They sat under the kitchen
and they could hear y'all.
You don't look dumb at all.
They look dumb and just like assholes.
-Yeah.
-It's just being an asshole.
It's okay. I don't want
to get you more hyped up.
-but that was just awful as fuck.
-The fact that. like...
If he said. "Hey...
there could be something
sparking with Kassy."
Yeah. they should both let you know.
I would've been like.
"Oh. my God. That's totally fine."
Don't be. Anna. she's still...
She's going to just sit down
like everything's cool?
And I didn't want to tell her
we overheard.
I feel like an idiot.
Like. I... It's embarrassing.
I trusted Leo. I trusted Kassy.
But I just keep getting thrown
different curve balls. and it hurts.
I owe it to myself. her and Anna.
to be honest on how I feel. right?
So. when I was saying.
when I see her around.
obviously. there's no denying
how we feel
when we see one another. right?
So. I had to get that off my chest.
'cause if she leaves.
I'll never ever have the chance
to say that.
-Doesn't look good. Le.
-I feel like a real important thing
that needed to be said to her
was that you were still.
like. open to talking.
Apparently. she didn't understand that.
Yeah. there was
no communication on that part.
I wasn't saying I was taking that route.
-Yeah. yeah. No. no. I...
-I'm just getting clarity
for the obvious vibe
that we still have for one another.
-Yeah. yeah. yeah.
-I couldn't hold that in my chest.
I'm going to talk to Anna
and tell her just that.
You should've pulled that chat with Anna
as soon as you could.
Oh. fuck me.
You know I totally support you guys
having that conversation
'cause you've been feeling
some type of way. But also.
I don't like that she was brought up
into the convo
'cause I guess she heard her name
and how he was saying...
He brought her up. yeah.
-And that's... that's not fair to her.
-Mm-mmm.
I also...
[sighs. whispering] I don't know. dude.
She feels betrayed by her friend
and her partner.
By both of us. yeah.
I don't know what I should do.
Should I pull her?
-Should I let Leo pull her first?
-What do you feel like?
-I wanna talk to her.
-You wanna get...
Honestly. go try. Go show that effort.
-If you wanna talk to her. go pull her.
-Yeah.
-Yeah. I do.
-At least try.
-Yeah.
-Get up there. babe.
-Fuck me.
-We all make...
-[phone chimes]
-Oh.
-Fuck.
[dramatic music playing]
Oh. fuck me in the fucking ass right now.
I got a text!
-Oh. my fucking goodness.
-[Harrison] Oh. nice.
-[woman] Shit.
-Goddamn.
[Kassy] Holy shit.
"Would all Islanders
please gather at the fire pit?
-#TheResultsAreIn."
-[Leonardo] Oh. God.
-[Keenan] Fuckin' hell.
-[Bergie] Shit.
[Hannah] End of the day. bitch. you safe.
Fuck this little-ass boy.
Fuck him.
[dramatic music continues]
I don't give second chances to idiots.
-Yeah. no. forget that.
-I never do. and I never will.
The disrespect is crazy.
Oh. my God.
I know. I didn't mean
to go about it like that.
-[Victor] Jesus.
-[Hannah] Fuck this.
Whatever happens happens.
[phone chimes]
[suspenseful music playing]
"Islanders. America has been voting
for their favorite couple.
Those with the fewest votes
risk being dumped tonight."
-[dramatic music playing]
-[phone chimes]
[sighs]
"Anna and Leonardo and Hannah and Marco.
as a result of yesterday's
Mr. and Mrs. Challenge.
you are not included in the vote."
[sighs]
["Rise and Fall" playing]
[phone chimes]
"Will all other Islanders please stand?"
♪ Waiting
We are patient ♪
[sighs]
♪ We hold our hands ♪
♪ And never let someone down ♪
[phone chimes]
"In no particular order.
the first couple saved by the public is...
♪ It's not easy ♪
♪ But we're not alone ♪
♪ In each other ♪
♪ We can find a home ♪
...Kay Kay and Keenan."
-♪ We rise ♪
-[clapping]
♪ And we fall ♪
♪ And we come back again ♪
-Fuck.
[both sigh]
♪ And fight
Let's fight till the end ♪
["Before the Whole Thing Blows" playing]
[sighs]
[phone chimes]
"The next couple saved is...
♪ The fire in the hole ♪
♪ Got to get out
Before the whole thing blows ♪
[music stops]
...Destiny and Harrison."
-Wow.
-[clapping]
[music resumes]
[Destiny chuckles]
-We did it.
-Well. of course.
[mouthing]
[suspenseful music plays]
-[phone chimes]
-Fuck.
[Keenan sighs]
"Only one more couple is safe."
Ooh.
[phone chimes]
"Third and final couple saved is..."
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
Before the break. Kay Kay and Keenan
and Destiny and Harrison were saved.
And you'll find out whether
Kassy and Bergie
or Carmen and Victor are also safe
as soon as I stop talking.
[phone chimes]
"The third and final couple saved is...
...Kassy and Bergie."
[mouths]
[phone chimes]
"Carmen and Victor.
please stand in front of the fire pit."
["Let Go of You" playing]
[sighs]
♪ Can you say that it's the end ♪
♪ So that I can let go of you? ♪
♪ You ♪
[phone chimes]
[gasps]
"Carmen and Victor.
as the bottom couple in the public vote.
you are now vulnerable.
However. only one of you
will leave the villa tonight.
[dramatic music plays]
Who goes and who stays
will be decided by your fellow Islanders."
Fuck.
["The Time of Our Lives" playing]
♪ It's the time of our lives ♪
Obviously. I feel like I've clicked
with Victor the most.
So. I mean. I would like to vote Victor.
Yeah. it's just very hard to me.
But when I came here.
I knew there were two things
you needed to do. and it was being honest
and looking for a romantic relationship.
I think this man tried to fulfill both.
So. I'm gonna go with Victor.
I'm voting for Carmen
because I feel like
she still hasn't found her person.
It could be Bergie. that's an option.
and I'm just voting for Carmen.
-That's all I have to say.
-I'm voting for Carmen. too.
Obviously. I came here
to find a romantic option.
so I'd like to vote for Carmen
just... just in case that...
the door's still open there.
I feel like Carmen really deserves this.
Besides that. me and her are really close.
She has been transparent. she's been open.
so I choose Carmen.
-What is that now?
-Four Carmen.
♪ It's the time of our lives ♪
I love them both.
-Y'all know I love them fuckin' both.
-[Kay Kay] Yeah.
But Victor has dove
just a little bit deeper.
I feel like Carmen's
still kind of waiting for that option.
We don't know if it's Bergie.
this. that and the third. I'mma go Victor.
I'm gonna add on to that point
and agree with you to go with Victor
because he's been open to go
beyond outside of his type
to look for his person.
So. it's four and four.
-[Keenan] Four and four.
-Okay.
I'm gonna vote Carmen
because. with Bergie.
she has a potential connection here.
That was. like... I don't even know
how that's like a fucking... I don't know.
[Bergie] Now it's on Destiny.
I'm sorry.
I didn't expect to be the deal breaker.
[sniffles. sighs]
Me. personally.
I'm going to have to vote for...
♪ This is the time our lives ♪
Victor.
Because he was the first person
to console me
when I went through everything.
-So...
-[Marco] Okay.
-[house music playing]
-It's five-five.
-Guys. we've gotta make a decision.
-[all chatter]
Either way. it's not... Tied or not.
-[Kay Kay] Who makes the overall decision?
-[Keenan] We need to.
-How do we do this. guys?
-I don't know. I'm just...
I don't know how to do this.
Berg. what do you think?
Do you think. in your heart.
that Carmen's gonna go for you?
I have no idea.
[sighs]
-I know.
-If it's not there. you gotta say it.
If it is there.
you gotta stick strong. bro.
Like. you gotta know.
Honestly. I'd rather risk it all.
-And that's perfectly fine.
-[Marco] That's fine.
-I'd rather risk it all on Carmen.
-That's okay.
I could see it working long term.
-I could...
-[Keenan] Yeah. yeah. I get it.
You made your decision.
If... If she swings.
she decides she doesn't want me.
I'll respect it. And I...
I'll admit that I fucked up.
Yeah. I'd rather go all in on Carmen
and see...
get burned later.
So. he's not swinging.
We're still split down the middle.
So. with Bergie expressing
his feelings about that.
does anybody want to support him
in that decision
and turn their vote to vote for Carmen
so he can have his chance to risk it all?
[Leonardo] Oh. my God.
♪ Time will wait for no-one ♪
[theme song playing]
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today